A Guide to the Philip S. Hench Walter Reed Yellow Fever Collection 1806-1995
Claude Moore Health Sciences Library
- DEPOSIT SLIP IN AMOUNT OF $5000 FOR JEFFERSON RANDOLPH KEAN 1900/11/15, DOCUMENT (Box-folder 021-080)
- LETTER FROM WALTER REED TO L.O. HOWARD 1900/11/16, ALS (P) (Box-folder 022-001)
- LETTER FROM L.O. HOWARD TO WALTER REED 1900/11/16, TLS (P) (Box-folder 022-002)
- AMERICAN VOLUNTEERS FOR EXPERIMENTAL YELLOW FEVER 1900/11/16, AMs (P) (2) (Box-folder 022-003)
- LETTER FROM GEORGE MILLER STERNBERG TO WALTER REED 1900/11/17, TLS (CC) (Box-folder 022-004)
- LETTER FROM LAWRENCE [WALTER L.] REED TO EMILIE LAWRENCE REED 1900/11/17, ALS (Box-folder 022-005)
- LETTER FROM WALTER REED TO EMILIE LAWRENCE REED 1900/11/18, ALS (Box-folder 022-006)
- LETTER FROM LAWRENCE [WALTER L.] REED TO EMILIE LAWRENCE REED 1900/11/19, ALS (Box-folder 022-007)
- LETTER FROM WALTER REED TO EMILIE LAWRENCE REED 1900/11/20, ALS (Box-folder 022-008)
- LETTER FROM WALTER REED TO EMILIE LAWRENCE REED 1900/11/21, ALS (Box-folder 022-009)
- ARTICLES ON YELLOW FEVER 1900/11/21, TMs (CC), AN (Box-folder 022-010)
  LA DISCUSION, WITH UNIDENTIFIED NOTE
- LETTER FROM L.O. HOWARD TO WALTER REED 1900/11/21, TLS (P) (Box-folder 022-011)
- HORRENDO..... SI ES CIERTO! 1900/11/22, TMs, NEWSPAPER CLIPPING (P) (Box-folder 022-012)
- LETTER FROM WALTER REED TO EMILIE LAWRENCE REED 1900/11/22, ALS (Box-folder 022-013)
- STATEMENT OF CUBAN VOLUNTEERS AS TO CONDITIONS FOR THEIR EXPERIMENTAL CASES OF YELLOW FEVER 1900/11/22, AMs (2) (Box-folder 022-014)
- CARTOON OF LEONARD WOOD AND ELIHU ROOT 1900/11/23, NEWSPAPER CLIPPING (P) (4) (Box-folder 022-015)
- DEL CONSULADO DE ESPANA 1900/11/23, NEWSPAPER CLIPPING (P) (Box-folder 022-016)
  [LA DISCUSION]
- LA FIEBRE AMARILLA 1900/11/24, NEWSPAPER CLIPPING (P) (Box-folder 022-017)
- LETTER FROM LAWRENCE [WALTER L.] REED TO EMILIE LAWRENCE REED 1900/11/25, ALS (Box-folder 022-018)
- LETTER FROM WALTER REED TO EMILIE LAWRENCE REED 1900/11/25, ALS (Box-folder 022-019)
- INFORMED CONSENT CONTRACTS OF SPANISH VOLUNTEERS FOR EXPERIMENTAL YELLOW FEVER 1900/11/26, TMsS (P) (Box-folder 022-020)
  IN ENGLISH AND SPANISH
- LETTER FROM WALTER REED TO EMILIE LAWRENCE REED 1900/11/27, ALS (Box-folder 022-021)
- LETTER FROM WALTER REED TO EMILIE LAWRENCE REED 1900/11/30, ALS, ALS (P) (2) (Box-folder 022-022)
- MONTHLY STATEMENT, DEPARTMENT OF FINANCE, ISLAND OF CUBA 1900/11, DOCUMENT (Box-folder 022-023)
- LETTER FROM WALTER REED TO EMILIE LAWRENCE REED 1900/11/02, ALS (Box-folder 022-024)
- LETTER FROM LAWRENCE [WALTER L.] REED TO EMILIE LAWRENCE REED 1900/12/04, ALS (Box-folder 022-025)
- LETTER FROM WALTER REED TO EMILIE LAWRENCE REED 1900/12/04, ALS (Box-folder 022-026)
- LETTER FROM CARLOS ROLFF TO JEFFERSON RANDOLPH KEAN 1900/12/06, TLS (Box-folder 022-027)
- LETTER FROM WALTER REED TO EMILIE LAWRENCE REED 1900/12/06, ALS (Box-folder 022-028)
- INFORMED CONSENT CONTRACT BETWEEN NICANAR FERNANDEZ AND WALTER REED 1900/12/08, TMsS (P) (2) (Box-folder 022-029)
- FEVER CHART FOR JOHN R. KISSINGER 1900/12/08-19, AMs (Box-folder 022-030)
- LETTER FROM WALTER REED TO EMILIE LAWRENCE REED 1900/12/09, AL (Box-folder 022-031)
  6 PAGES WITH ENVELOPE (FRAGMENT)
- LETTER FROM WALTER REED TO ALBERT E. TRUBY 1900/12/10, ALS (P) (9) (Box-folder 022-032)
- LETTER FROM WALTER REED TO EMILIE LAWRENCE REED 1900/12/11, ALS (Box-folder 022-033)
- A CURE FOR CONSUMPTION? 1900/12/11, NEWSPAPER CLIPPING (P) (Box-folder 022-034)
- LETTER FROM WALTER REED TO EMILIE LAWRENCE REED 1900/12/12, AL (Box-folder 022-035)
- FEVER CHART FOR ANTONIO PENINO 1900/12/12-19, AMs, AMs (P) (Box-folder 022-036)
- LETTER FROM WILLIAM CRAWFORD GORGAS TO HENRY ROSE CARTER 1900/12/13, TLS (Box-folder 022-037)
- LETTER FROM WALTER REED TO EMILIE LAWRENCE REED 1900/12/13, ALS (Box-folder 022-038)
- LETTER FROM LEONARD WOOD TO ADJUTANT GENERAL 1900/12/13, TLS (P) (Box-folder 022-039)
- LETTER FROM WALTER REED TO EMILIE LAWRENCE REED 1900/12/14, AL, AL (P) (2) (Box-folder 022-040)
  4 PAGES WITH ENVELOPE (FRAGMENT)
- FEVER CHARTS FOR NICANOR FERNANDEZ 1900/12/14-20, AMs (2), AMs (P) (2) (Box-folder 022-041)
- LETTER FROM LAWRENCE [WALTER L.] REED TO EMILIE LAWRENCE REED 1900/12/14, ALS (Box-folder 022-042)
- TELEGRAM FROM WALTER REED TO WAR DEPARTMENT 1900/12/15, TELEGRAM (P) (Box-folder 022-043)
  MOSQUITO THEORY PROVEN
- FEVER CHART FOR BECIENTE PRESIDO 1900/12/15-28, AMs, AMs (P) (2) (Box-folder 022-044)
- LETTER FROM WALTER REED TO EMILIE LAWRENCE REED 1900/12/16, ALS (Box-folder 022-045)
- LETTER FROM WALTER REED TO WAR DEPARTMENT 1900/12/16, TELEGRAM (P) (Box-folder 022-046)
  CONFIRMATION OF VICTORY OVER YELLOW FEVER
- LETTER FROM GEORGE MILLER STERNBERG TO WALTER REED 1900/12/17, TELEGRAM (P) (Box-folder 022-047)
  CONGRATULATIONS EXTENDED
- LETTER FROM WALTER REED TO EMILIE LAWRENCE REED 1900/12/18, ALS (Box-folder 022-048)
- MOSQUITOES AND YELLOW FEVER 1900/12/18, NEWSPAPER CLIPPING (P) (Box-folder 022-049)
- LETTER FROM GEORGE MILLER STERNBERG TO WALTER REED 1900/12/19, TLS (CC) (Box-folder 022-050)
- GENERAL ORDERS NO. 6 1900/12/21, REPORT (P) (Box-folder 022-051)
  MOSQUITOES
- STILL FUMBLING WITH YELLOW FEVER 1900/12/22, NEWSPAPER CLIPPING (P) (Box-folder 022-052)
- EN HONOR DEL DR. FINLAY 1900/12/22, NEWSPAPER CLIPPING (P) (Box-folder 022-053)
- LETTER FROM WALTER REED TO EMILIE LAWRENCE REED 1900/12/23, ALS (Box-folder 022-054)
- LETTER FROM WALTER REED TO ADJUTANT GENERAL 1900/12/24, TLS (P) (2) (Box-folder 022-055)
- FEVER CHART FOR JOHN J. MORAN 1900/12/24-1901/01/02, AMs, AMs (P) (Box-folder 022-056)
- LETTER FROM WALTER REED TO EMILIE LAWRENCE REED 1900/12/25-26, ALS (Box-folder 022-057)
  9 PAGES WITH ENVELOPE COMMENTS ON WORK WITH MOSQUITOES
- LETTER FROM WALTER REED TO EMILIE LAWRENCE REED 1900/12/28, ALS (Box-folder 022-058)
- LETTER FROM WALTER REED TO EMILIE LAWRENCE REED 1900/12/28/ca., AL (Box-folder 022-059)
- LETTER FROM JEFFERSON RANDOLPH KEAN TO TREASURER, ISLAND OF CUBA 1900/12/29, TLS (Box-folder 022-060)
- LETTER FROM WALTER REED TO EMILIE LAWRENCE REED 1900/12/30, ALS (Box-folder 022-061)
- LETTER FROM WALTER REED TO EMILIE LAWRENCE REED 1900/12/31-1901/01/01, ALS, NEGATIVES (3) (Box-folder 022-062)
  10 PAGES WITH ENVELOPE FAMOUS NEW YEAR'S EVE LETTER
- LETTER FROM LAWRENCE [WALTER L.] REED TO EMILIE LAWRENCE REED 1900/12/31, ALS (Box-folder 022-063)
- FRAGMENT OF RECORD FOR JOHN J. KISSINGER'S CASE OF YELLOW FEVER IN WALTER REED'S HANDWRITING 1900/12, AMs (P) (Box-folder 022-064)
  NOTE BY LAWRENCE [WALTER L.] REED
- MEMORANDUM OF THE MISSTATEMENTS ATTRIBUTED TO GENERAL WOOD IN PUBLISHED INTERVIEWS AND MADE BY HIM IN FORMAL COMMUNICATIONS BY WILLIAM LUDLOW 1900/12, REPORT (P) (Box-folder 022-065)
  13 PAGES
- PAGES FROM WALTER REED'S RECORDS OF EXPERIMENTAL YELLOW FEVER 1900, AMs (P) (Box-folder 022-066)
  CHARTS FOR ANTONIO, BENIGNO, NICONAR, FERNANDEZ, BECIENTE, PRECADO, MORAN, MARTINEZ, JERNIGAN, OLSEN, LOUSTAGG, SPRINGER, FOLK, HANBERRY, FORBES, KISSINGER, WEST, AMES, WEATHERWALK
- SPECIAL ORDERS FOR ARMY OFFICERS AND MEDICAL MEN IN CUBA 1900, *REPORTS (P) (Box-folder 022-067)
- FEVER CHART FOR JEFFERSON RANDOLPH KEAN 1900, AMs (P) (Box-folder 022-068)
  INCLUDES NOTES ON CONDITION, TREATMENT 21 JUNE TO 30 JUNE 1900
- PAGES FROM DIARY OF JEFFERSON RANDOLPH KEAN 1900, AMs, AMs (P) (Box-folder 022-069)
  WITH NOTES BY J.R. KEAN
- RESOLUTION CONCERNING DR. JESSE W. LAZEAR 1900, TMs (Box-folder 023-001)
- CASES OF YELLOW FEVER: RECORDS ON MOSQUITOES 1900, AMs (P) (Box-folder 023-002)
- DEATHS DUE TO YELLOW FEVER 1900, *TELEGRAMS (P) (Box-folder 023-003)
- WORLD ALMANAC AND ENCYCLOPEDIA CALENDAR 1900, CALENDAR (P) (Box-folder 023-004)
- MORTUARY RECORD OF YELLOW FEVER IN HAVANA 1884-1900 1900, TMs (CC) (Box-folder 023-005)
- MILITARY RECORDS FOR WALTER REED 1900, AMs (P), TMs (P) (Box-folder 023-006)
- PAGES FROM LAZEAR-REED NOTEBOOK 1900, AMs (P) (Box-folder 023-007)
- MICROFILM COPY OF PAGES FROM LAZEAR-REED NOTEBOOK 1900, AMs (P) (Box-folder 023-008)
- PAGES FROM LAZEAR'S LABORATORY NOTEBOOK 1900, AMs (P) (Box-folder 023-009)
  ca. SPRING
- STUDENT OF YELLOW FEVER 1900/ca., NEWSPAPER CLIPPING (P) (Box-folder 023-010)
  CHICAGO RECORD
- PAGES FROM LAZEAR-REED NOTEBOOK 1900-1901, AMs (P) (Box-folder 023-011)
  RE JOHN J. MORAN
- MAJOR JEFFERSON RANDOLPH KEAN'S EXPENSE ACCOUNT FOR CAMP LAZEAR 1900-1901, TMs, TMs (CC) (2) (Box-folder 023-012)
- CIRCULARS CONCERNING DETECTION OF YELLOW FEVER AND PREVENTION OF DISEASE 1900, *REPORTS (P) (Box-folder 023-013)
- CHART OF YELLOW FEVER MOSQUITOES 1900, AMs (P) (Box-folder 023-014)
- SPECIAL ORDERS CONCERNING MILITARY AND MEDICAL FIGURES IN CUBA 1900, *REPORTS (P) (Box-folder 023-015)
- ARTICLES SENT TO PHILIP SHOWALTER HENCH BY MARIA TERESA ROJAS 1900, TMs (Box-folder 023-016)
  THE LUCHA
- REPORT OF THE SECRETARY OF JUSTICE FROM JULY 1ST, 1899 TO JUNE 30, 1900 1900, REPORT (Box-folder 023-017)
- ARISTIDES AGRAMONTE'S RECORD OF MOSQUITO BITES AND RESULTING CASES OF YELLOW FEVER 1900, AMs (P) (Box-folder 023-018)
- RECORD OF YELLOW FEVER CASES TREATED AT COLUMBIA BARRACKS 1900, AMs (P) (Box-folder 023-019)
- PERSONAL REPORTS OF ARISTIDES AGRAMONTE 1900, AMs (P) (Box-folder 023-020)
- LIST OF MOSQUITOES 1900, AMs (P) (Box-folder 023-021)
- SPECIAL ORDERS FOR ARISTIDES AGRAMONTE 1900, *REPORTS (P) (Box-folder 023-022)
- RECORD OF YELLOW FEVER CHARTS 1900, AMs (P) (Box-folder 023-023)
- SPECIAL ORDERS AND CIRCULARS CONCERNING MILITARY AND MEDICAL MEN IN CUBA 1900, *REPORTS (P) (Box-folder 023-024)
- INNOCULATION OF NONIMMUNE INDIVIDUALS THROUGH THE BITE OF MOSQUITOES (CULEX FASCIATUS) 1900/ca., CHART (P) (Box-folder 023-025)
- PLAN OF WALTER REED'S QUARTERS IN BUILDING 108 AT COLUMBIA BARRACK, LABORATORY BUILDING PLAN 1900, DIAGRAM, DIAGRAMS (P) (6) (Box-folder 023-026)
- SHOULDER STRAP WORN BY WALTER REED 1900/ca., ARTIFACT, ANS (Box-folder 023-027)
  PRESENTED TO PHILIP SHOWALTER HENCH FROM BLOSSOM REED, DECEMBER 16, 1943
- MILITARY ORDERS FOR WALTER REED 1901, AMs (P), TMs (P) (Box-folder 024-001)
- L.H. MATTINGLY TO JEFFERSON RANDOLPH KEAN 1901/01/03, TLS (Box-folder 024-002)
- LETTER FROM WALTER REED TO EMILIE LAWRENCE REED 1901/01/03-05, ALS (Box-folder 024-003)
- LETTER FROM WALTER REED TO EMILIE LAWRENCE REED 1901/01/05-07, ALS (Box-folder 024-004)
- LETTER FROM L.O. HOWARD TO WALTER REED 1901/01/05, TLS (P) (Box-folder 024-005)
- LETTER FROM WALTER REED TO EMILIE LAWRENCE REED 1901/01/07, ALS (Box-folder 024-006)
- LETTER FROM LAWRENCE [WALTER L.] REED TO EMILIE LAWRENCE REED 1901/01/07, ALS (Box-folder 024-007)
- GEORGE MILLER STERNBERG TO JAMES DALY, WALTER REED 1901/01/08, TLS (CC) (2) (Box-folder 024-008)
- FEVER CHART FOR WARREN G. JERNEGAN (WITH STATEMENT RE HOSPITALIZATION) 1901/01/08-16, AMs, TMsS, AMs (P), TMsS (P) (Box-folder 024-009)
- FEVER CHART FOR WILLIAM OLSEN (WITH STATEMENT RE HOSPITALIZATION) 1901/01/10-19, AMs, TMsS, AMs (P). TMsS (P) (Box-folder 024-010)
- CARRIER OF YELLOW FEVER 1901/01/10, NEWSPAPER CLIPPING (P) (Box-folder 024-011)
- CARRY YELLOW FEVER GERMS 1901/01/10, NEWSPAPER CLIPPING (P) (Box-folder 024-012)
- LETTER FROM L.O. HOWARD TO WALTER REED 1901/01/10, TLS (P) (Box-folder 024-013)
- LETTER FROM WALTER REED TO EMILIE LAWRENCE REED 1901/01/11, ALS (Box-folder 024-014)
- LETTER FROM WILLIAM CRAWFORD GORGAS TO ADJUTANT GENERAL 1901/01/12, TLS (P) (Box-folder 024-015)
- LETTER FROM WALTER REED TO EMILIE LAWRENCE REED 1901/01/13/ca., AENVELOPE (Box-folder 024-016)
- YELLOW FEVER MOSQUITOES 1891/01/13, NEWSPAPER CLIPPING (P) (Box-folder 024-017)
- LETTER FROM LAWRENCE [WALTER L.] REED TO EMILIE LAWRENCE REED 1901/01/14, ALS (Box-folder 024-018)
  5 PAGES WITH ENVELOPE
- WALTER REED TO L.O. HOWARD 1901/01/15, ALS (P) (Box-folder 024-019)
- LETTER FROM L.O. HOWARD TO WALTER REED 1901/01/17, TLS (Box-folder 024-020)
- LETTER FROM GEORGE MILLER STERNBERG TO ADJUTANT GENERAL 1901/01/17, TLS (P) (2) (Box-folder 024-021)
- VALUABLE DISCOVERIES IN HAVANA 1901/01/17, NEWSPAPER CLIPPING (P) (Box-folder 024-022)
- LETTER FROM H.F. JACKSON TO CHAUNCEY B. BAKER 1901/01/17, TLS (P) (Box-folder 024-023)
- LETTER FROM WALTER REED TO EMILIE LAWRENCE REED 1901/01/18, ALS (Box-folder 024-024)
- LETTER FROM WALTER REED TO EMILIE LAWRENCE REED 1901/01/21, ALS (Box-folder 024-025)
- LETTER FROM HUGH L. SCOTT TO HARRY FREDERICK JACKSON 1901/01/21, TLS (P) (Box-folder 024-026)
- LETTER FROM L.O. HOWARD TO WALTER REED 1901/01/22, TLS (P) (Box-folder 024-027)
- FEVER CHART FOR ROGER POST AMES 1901/01/26-02/03, AMs, AMs (P) (2) (Box-folder 024-028)
- SPECIAL ORDERS NO. 22 1901/01/26, REPORT (P) (Box-folder 024-029)
  RE: JEFFERSON R. KEAN
- LETTER FROM WALTER REED TO EMILIE LAWRENCE REED 1901/01/27, ALS (Box-folder 024-030)
- FEVER CHART FOR JOHN H. ANDRUS 1901/01/28-02/08, AMs (Box-folder 024-031)
- LETTER FROM WALTER REED TO EMILIE LAWRENCE REED 1901/02/03, ALS (Box-folder 024-032)
- FEVER CHART FOR CLYDE L. WEST (WITH VERIFICATION OF HOSPITALIZATION) 1901/02/03-10, AMs, TMsS, AMs (P), TMsS (P) (Box-folder 024-033)
- PERMISSION FOR JOHN R. KISSINGER TO VISIT HAVANA 1901/02/04, AMs (P) (Box-folder 024-034)
- THE QUESTIONS OF THE DAY 1901/02/08, NEWSPAPER CLIPPING (P) (Box-folder 024-035)
- CARTOON 1901/02/08, NEWSPAPER CLIPPINGS (P) (3) (Box-folder 024-036)
- DIARIO DE LA MARINA (HAVANA) 1901/02/08, NEWSPAPER CLIPPING (P) (Box-folder 024-037)
- FEVER CHART FOR JAMES L. HANBERRY (WITH VERIFICATION OF HOSPITALIZATION) 1901/02/09-19, AMs, TMsS (Box-folder 024-038)
- FEVER CHART FOR CHARLES G. SONTAG (WITH VERIFICATION OF HOSPITALIZATION) 1901/02/10, AMs, TMsS, AMs (P), TMsS (P) (Box-folder 024-039)
- LETTER FROM JAMES CARROLL TO L.O. HOWARD 1901/02/10, ALS (P) (Box-folder 024-040)
- THE LATEST ABOUT YELLOW FEVER 1901/02/11, NEWSPAPER CLIPPING (P) (Box-folder 024-041)
- LETTER FROM L.O. HOWARD TO JAMES CARROLL 1901/02/14, TLS (P) (Box-folder 024-042)
- LETTER FROM WALTER REED TO JAMES CARROLL 1901/02/16, TL (CC), TL (P) (Box-folder 024-043)
- VERIFICATION OF HOSPITALIZATION OF ROGER POST AMES AND CERFITICATION OF YELLOW FEVER DIAGNOSIS 1901/02/16, TMsS (P) (Box-folder 024-044)
- LETTER FROM GEORGE M. KOBER TO HOWARD A. KELLY 1901/02/20, ALS (Box-folder 024-045)
- OUR DUTY IN CUBA, THE MOSQUITO AND THE FROST 1901/02/23, NEWSPAPER CLIPPINGS (P) (2) (Box-folder 024-046)
- LETTER FROM WALTER REED TO HENRY ROSE CARTER 1901/02/26, TL (CC) (Box-folder 024-047)
- LETTER FROM WALTER REED TO ADJUTANT GENERAL 1901/02/28, TLS (P) (Box-folder 024-048)
- LIST OF YELLOW FEVER PATIENTS AT COLUMBIA BARRACKS, DECEMBER 1900-FEBRUARY 1901 1901/02, AMs (P) (Box-folder 024-049)
- LETTER FROMJOHN J. MORAN TO JEFFERSON RANDOLPH KEAN 1901/03/02, ALS (Box-folder 024-050)
- LETTER FROM WALTER REED TO ROGER POST AMES "1901/03/11, 26", ALS (P) (2) (Box-folder 024-051)
  4 PAGES, 2 PAGES
- THE QUESTIONS OF THE DAY 1901/03/26, NEWSPAPER CLIPPING (P) (Box-folder 024-052)
- LETTER FROM WALTER REED TO ROGER POST AMES 1901/03/28, TLS (P) (Box-folder 024-053)
- YELLOW FEVER EXPERIMENTS 1901/03/31, NEWSPAPER CLIPPING (P) (Box-folder 024-054)
- THE ETIOLOGY OF YELLOW FEVER 1901/03/31, NEWSPAPER CLIPPING (P) (Box-folder 024-055)
- LETTER FROM WALTER REED TO HENRY ROSE CARTER 1901/04/03, TL (COPY) (Box-folder 024-056)
  TYPED COPY BY H. CARTER REDD
- A PROJECT IN HAVANA 1901/04/06, NEWSPAPER CLIPPING (P) (Box-folder 024-057)
- LETTER FROM R.M. O'REILLY TO SURGEON GENERAL 1901/04/05, TLS (P) (Box-folder 024-058)
- YELLOW FEVER GERMS 1901/04/08, NEWSPAPER CLIPPING (P) (Box-folder 024-059)
- WHAT SURGEON GENERAL STERNBERG SAYS 901/04/19, NEWSPAPER CLIPPING (P) (Box-folder 024-060)
- REPORT 1901/04/20, TMs (CC) (Box-folder 024-061)
- CAUSES YELLOW FEVER 1901/04/24, NEWSPAPER CLIPPING (Box-folder 024-062)
  THE BALTIMORE NEWS
- CIRCULAR: YELLOW FEVER AND FOMITES 1901/04/27, REPORT (P) (Box-folder 024-063)
- CORRESPONDENCE BETWEEN GEORGE JONES AND GIBSON BROTHERS 1901/04/06, TLS (P). ALS (P) (Box-folder 024-064)
- LETTER FORM WALTER REED TO ARISTIDES AGRAMONTE 1901/05/02, ALS (P) (4) (Box-folder 024-065)
- LETTER FORM GEORGE MILLER STERNBERG TO ARISTIDES AGRAMONTE 1901/05/10, TLS (P) (Box-folder 024-066)
  REQUESTS PERSONAL DATA
- LETTER FROM SURGEON GENERAL TO LORD PAUNCEFOOTE 1901/05/14, TL (P) (Box-folder 024-067)
- VALERY HAVARD TO SURGEON GENERAL 1901/05/16, TLS (P) (3) (Box-folder 024-068)
  QUERIES IF AGRAMONTE HAS BEEN RELIEVED
- LETTER FROM LORD PAUNCEFOOTE TO SURGEON GENERAL 1901/05/16, TLS (P) (Box-folder 024-069)
- LETTER FROM ROBERT M. O'REILLY TO ROGER POST AMES 1901/05/19, ALS (P) (Box-folder 024-070)
- LETTER FROM GEORGE MILLER STERNBERG TO ADJUTANT GENERAL 1901/05/12, TLS (P) (2) (Box-folder 024-071)
  AGRAMONTE RELIEVED
- CABLE AND SPECIAL ORDERS RE: REMOVAL OF ARISTIDES AGRAMONTE FROM BOARD 1901/05/21, CABLE (P), REPORTS (P) (Box-folder 024-072)
- LETTER FROM WALTER REED TO JEFFERSON RANDOLPH KEAN 1901/05/23, ALS (P) (Box-folder 024-073)
- SURGEON GENERAL CIRCULAR - GEORGE MILLER STERNBERG 1901/05/26, NEWSPAPER CLIPPING (P) (Box-folder 024-074)
- STATEMENT OF ADMITTANCE TO HOSPITAL AND CERTIFICATION OF YELLOW FEVER DIAGNOSIS - RE: JOHN R. KISSINGER 1901/05/30, TMsS (P) (4) (Box-folder 024-075)
- LETTER FROM WALTER REED TO ROGER POST AMES 1901/05/31, ALS (P) (Box-folder 024-076)
- LETTER FROM JOHN HAY TO SECRETARY OF WAR 1901/05/31, TLS (P) (Box-folder 024-077)
- LETTER FROM GEORGE MILLER STERNBERG TO SECRETARY OF STATE 1901/06/03, TLS (P) (Box-folder 025-001)
- ASSISTANT SECRETARY OF WAR TO JOHN HAY 1901/06/04, TLS (P) (Box-folder 025-002)
- LETTER FROM WALTER REED TO JEFFERSON RANDOLPH KEAN VIA GEORGE MILLER STERNBERG 1901/06/05, ALS, ALS (P) (Box-folder 025-003)
- LETTER FROM S.M. SPARKMAN TO GEORGE MILLER STERNBERG 1901/06/05, TLS (P) (Box-folder 025-004)
- MOSQUITOES' DEADLY WORK 1901/06/05, NEWSPAPER CLIPPING (P) (Box-folder 025-005)
- LETTER FROM SURGEON GENERAL TO S.M. SPARKMAN 1901/06/07, TL (P) (Box-folder 025-006)
- LETTER FROM S.M. SPARKMAN TO GEORGE MILLER STERNBERG 1901/06/08, TLS (P) (Box-folder 025-007)
- LETTER FROM GEORGE MILLER STERNBERG TO S.M. SPARKMAN 1901/06/11, TLS (P) (Box-folder 025-008)
- LETTER FROM GEORGE MILLER STERNBERG TO S.M. SPARKMAN 1901/06/13, TLS (P) (Box-folder 025-009)
- LETTER FROM VALERY HAVARD TO ADJUTANT GENERAL 1901/06/19, TLS (P) (Box-folder 025-010)
- LETTER FROM A.H. GLENNAN TO ADJUTANT GENERAL 1901/06/25, TLS (P) (Box-folder 025-011)
- LETTER FROM L.O. HOWARD TO JAMES CARROLL 1901/07/05, TLS (P) (Box-folder 025-012)
- CIRCULAR NO. 2 1901/07/09, REPORT (P) (Box-folder 025-013)
  TRANSMISSION OF MALARIA AND YELLOW FEVER BY MOSQUITOES
- THE SUPPRESSION OF YELLOW FEVER 1901/07/11, NEWSPAPER CLIPPING (P) (Box-folder 025-014)
- LETTER FROM WALTER REED TO THEOBALD SMITH 1901/07/19, ALS (Box-folder 025-015)
  3 PAGES RE MOSQUITO CULTURES AND BACILLUS ICTEROIDES
- REPORT OF MAJOR VALERY HAVARD, SURGEON U.S. ARMY, DEPARTMENT OF CUBA 1901, REPORT (Box-folder 025-016)
- SPECIAL ORDERS NO. 164 - MILITARY ORDERS FOR THOMAS M. ENGLAND 1901/07/31, REPORT (P) (Box-folder 025-017)
  RE THOMAS M. ENGLAND
- LETTERS RE: PHILIPPI CALDAS AND HIS YELLOW FEVER SERUS 1901/07-08, *ALS (P), TLS (P) (Box-folder 025-018)
- SPECIAL ORDERS NO. 166 1901/08/03, REPORT (P) (Box-folder 025-019)
  GUSTAF E. LAMBERT TRANSFERRED TO PIROTECNIA MILITAR, HAVANA
- CIRCULAR LETTER NO. 59 1901/08/07, TL (P) (Box-folder 025-020)
- NEWSPAPER CLIPPING RE: WALTER REED AND CARLOS FINLAY 1901/08/08, NEWSPAPER CLIPPING (Box-folder 025-021)
- SPECIAL ORDERS NO. 171 - MILITARY ORDERS 1901/08/10, REPORT (P) (Box-folder 025-022)
  RE WALLACE W. FORBES AND HENRY DELAMAR
- LETTER FROM JAMES CARROLL TO WALTER REED 1901/08/11, TL (P) (Box-folder 025-023)
- LETTER FROM HUGH L. SCOTT TO WILLIAM CRAWFORD GORGAS 1901/08/15, TLS (P) (Box-folder 025-024)
  RE FUNDS FOR CARROLL'S WORK WITH YELLOW FEVER
- MORTGAGE FOR MARYLAND PROPERTY OF WALTER REED AND EMILIE LAWRENCE REED 1901/08/29-30, TMs (P) (Box-folder 025-025)
- CARTOON ABOUT 'VOLUNTEERS' FOR YELLOW FEVER 1901/08/23, NEWSPAPER CLIPPING (P) (Box-folder 025-026)
- TYPESCRIPT OF LETTERS BETWEEN WALTER REED AND JAMES CARROLL 1901/08, TMs, AMs (Box-folder 025-027)
- FEVER CHART FOR CLARA L. MAASS 1901/08/14-25, AMs (Box-folder 025-028)
- THE THIRD MOSQUITO VICTIM 1901/08/25, NEWSPAPER CLIPPING (P) (Box-folder 025-029)
- THE MARTYRS OF SCIENCE 1901/08/27, NEWSPAPER CLIPPING (P) (Box-folder 025-030)
- ARTICLE RE: YELLOW FEVER EXPERIMENTS 1901/08/01, NEWSPAPER CLIPPING (Box-folder 025-031)
- LETTER FROM JEFFERSON RANDOLPH KEAN TO ROGER POST AMES 1901/08/03, ALS (P) (Box-folder 025-032)
- YELLOW FEVER AND QUARANTINE 1901/09/3, NEWSPAPER CLIPPING (P) (Box-folder 025-033)
- MOSQUITOES AND MALARIA 1901/09/07, NEWSPAPER CLIPPING (Box-folder 025-034)
  THE MEDICAL RECORD
- PAPERS AND REPORTS FROM THE TWENTY-NINTH ANNUAL MEETING OF THE AMERICAN PUBLIC HEALTH ASSOCIATION 1901/09/16-20, *REPORTS (P) (Box-folder 025-035)
- LETTER FROM JAMES CARROLL TO WALTER REED 1901/09/22, TL (TYPESCRIPT) (P) (Box-folder 025-036)
- LETTER FORM JAMES CARROLL TO WALTER REED 1901/09/24, TL (TYPESCRIPT) (Box-folder 025-037)
- LETTER FROM WALTER REED TO JEFFERSON RANDOLPH KEAN 1901/09/24, ALS (P) (Box-folder 025-038)
- LETTER FROM WALTER REED TO JAMES CARROLL 1901/09/30, ALS (Box-folder 025-039)
- LETTER FROM JAMES CARROLL TO L.O. HOWARD 1901/10/03, ALS (P) (Box-folder 025-040)
- LETTER FROM T.H. CHITTINDEN TO JAMES CARROLL 1901/10/09, TLS (P) (Box-folder 025-041)
- LETTER FROM JAMES CARROLL TO L.O. HOWARD 1901/10/10, ALS (P) (Box-folder 025-042)
- LETTER FROM JEFFERSON RANDOLPH KEAN TO WALTER REED 1901/10/13, ALS (Box-folder 025-043)
  6 PAGES WITH ENVELOPE KEAN SUPPORTS REED FOR NEW SURGEON GENERAL
- TELEGRAM FROM JAMES CARROLL TO WAR DEPARTMENT 1901/10/22, TELEGRAM (P) (Box-folder 025-044)
- LIST OF MEN UNDERGOING YELLOW FEVER EXPERIMENTS 1901/10/23, AMs (Box-folder 025-045)
- LETTER FROM T.H. CHITTINDEN TO JAMES CARROLL 1901/10/23, TLS (P) (Box-folder 025-046)
- J.F. DUNSHIE INQUIRES AS TO REASON FOR ANNULMENT OF HIS CONTRACT AS ARMY DOCTOR 1901/10/23, TMs (CC) (Box-folder 025-047)
- LETTER FROM WALTER REED TO JEFFERSON RANDOLPH KEAN 1901/11/05, ALS (Box-folder 025-048)
  4 PAGES WITH ENVELOPE REED URGES KEAN TO SEEK OFFICE OF SURGEON GENERAL
- LETTER FROM JOHN GUITERAS TO ROGER POST AMES 1901/11/05, ALS (P) (Box-folder 025-049)
- LETTER FROM JEFFERSON RANDOLPH KEAN TO WALTER REED 1901/11/09, TLS (Box-folder 025-050)
  4 PAGES WITH ENVELOPE KEAN SUPPORTS REED AS NEW SURGEON GENERAL
- REFERENCE FOR GUSTAV E. LAMBERT 1901/11/12, TMsS (Box-folder 025-051)
- LETTER FROM JEFFERSON RANDOLPH KEAN TO WALTER REED 1901/11/26, ALS (Box-folder 025-052)
  4 PAGES WITH ENVELOPE RE REED'S CANDIDACY FOR SURGEON GENERAL
- LETTER FROM L.O. HOWARD TO WALTER REED 1901/12/10, TLS (P) (Box-folder 025-053)
- LETTER FROM WALTER REED TO ROGER POST AMES 1901/12/21, ALS (P) (Box-folder 025-054)
- LETTER FROM WALTER REED TO ALBERT ROBIN 1901/12/21, TL (Box-folder 025-055)
- SPECIAL ORDERS NO. 280 - MILITARY ORDERS 1901/12/23, REPORT (P) (Box-folder 025-056)
  RE JOHN J. MORAN (NOT MORAN ASSOCIATED WITH YELLOW FEVER EXPERIMENTS)
- LETTER FROM ROGER POST AMES TO SURGEON GENERAL 1901/12/30, TLS (P) (Box-folder 025-057)
- LETTER FROM LEONARD WOOD TO JOHN DLAZELL 1901/12/31, TLS (Box-folder 025-058)
  1 PAGE RE PENSION FOR MRS. LAZEAR
- SPECIAL ORDERS, DEPARTMENT OF CUBA 1901, REPORT (P) (Box-folder 025-059)
- PAGES FROM DR. ROJAS' DAY BOOK 1901, AMs (P) (Box-folder 025-060)
- WALTER REED AND YELLOW FEVER: CHRONOLOGY OF THE YELLOW FEVER WORK IN CUBA, 1899 AND 1900 AND PERSONAL EXPERIENCES 1901, TMs (CC) (Box-folder 025-061)
  WITH AA BY PHILIP SHOWALTER HENCH
- REQUISITION AND ESTIMATE FOR INSULAR FUNDS 1901, REPORT (P) (Box-folder 025-062)
- SPECIAL ORDERS - MILITARY ORDERS 1901, *REPORTS (P) (Box-folder 025-063)
  RE ARISTIDES AGRAMONTE
- SPECIAL ORDERS - MILITARY ORDERS 1901, *REPORTS (P) (Box-folder 025-064)
  RE JAMES CARROLL
- SPECIAL ORDERS - MILITARY ORDERS 1901, *REPORTS (P) (Box-folder 025-065)